<znai>
  <entry>
    <url>/mantaro-wiki</url>
    <fullTitle>Your Product Your product</fullTitle>
    <text>
      <text>quick summaryNote: This is a summary page for your product. It is your landing page, but is not a part of your Table Of Contents. If you don't know what to put here use :include-redirect: chapter-title/page-title to automatically redirect to a page in your Table Of Contents.</text>
      <score>STANDARD</score>
    </text>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <url>/mantaro-wiki/chapter-one/getting-started#main-concepts</url>
    <fullTitle>Your Product: Getting Started, Main Concepts [Chapter One]</fullTitle>
    <text>
      <text>Znai has three levels of documentation organization:Chapters Pages Page Sections Znai encourages authors to split their content across multiple pages.If you feel like you need to use nested headings, consider moving your content hierarchy one level up:Split overlong page into multiple ones Introduce chapters Focus on one thing at a time It may help to show parallel with OOP conceptsChapters as packages Pages as classes Page Sections as methods It is a bad practice to have a class with loosely related methods. Similarly, it is a bad practice to have a long page with loosely related sections. https://testingisdocumenting.org/znai/flow/structure Read more</text>
      <score>STANDARD</score>
    </text>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <url>/mantaro-wiki/chapter-one/getting-started#table-of-contents</url>
    <fullTitle>Your Product: Getting Started, Table of Contents [Chapter One]</fullTitle>
    <text>
      <text>Each documentation must have toc file in its root. This file contains chapters and pages.This is a toc file for this auto generated documentation. chapter-one getting-started page-two chapter-two page-three page-four Take a look at the left side bar and compare it with the file content.The top entry, Chapter One , corresponds to the directory chapter-one . The nested entries like Page Two , corresponds to the file page-two.md .</text>
      <score>STANDARD</score>
    </text>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <url>/mantaro-wiki/chapter-one/getting-started#embedding-content</url>
    <fullTitle>Your Product: Getting Started, Embedding Content [Chapter One]</fullTitle>
    <text>
      <text>To reduce documentation maintenance burden avoid copy and paste of code snippets. Embed content by referencing existing files using :include-file: plugin instead. :include-file: file-name.js {title: "Optional Title"} class JsClass { constructor() { } } export default JsClass File will be looked up using following rules:directory with a markup file root directory of a documentation all lookup paths listed in a lookup-paths file https://testingisdocumenting.org/znai/snippets/external-code-snippets Read more</text>
      <score>STANDARD</score>
    </text>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <url>/mantaro-wiki/chapter-one/getting-started#meta</url>
    <fullTitle>Your Product: Getting Started, Meta [Chapter One]</fullTitle>
    <text>
      <text>Each documentation must have the meta.json file in its root. This JSON file contains documentation display name, type, and optional View On information. { "title": "Your Product", "type": "Guide", "viewOn": { "link": "your-custom-base-url", "title": "View On Label" } }</text>
      <score>STANDARD</score>
    </text>
  </entry>
</znai>
